n1bestfreeclassifiedads.com 2016-11-27

# N1best Free Classified Ads Free Classifiedads Free Advertising Free ad Services Free Classified Trading Free Marketing Classifiedad

1\. Introduction

Cookies Policy

(1) Introduction

Our website uses cookies.

We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

(2) About cookies

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and identify users returning to a website. 

Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies.

A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date).

A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

(3) Our cookies

We use only session cookies 

(5) Third party and analytics cookies

When you use our website, you may also be sent third party cookies.

Our advertisers and service providers may send you cookies. They may use the information they obtain from your use of their cookies:

(a) to track your browser across multiple websites;

(b) to build a profile of your web surfing; and

(c) to target advertisements which may be of particular interest to you.

In addition, we use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. [Google Analytics] generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html

The inclusion of this statement in your privacy policy will not in itself satisfy the requirements of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 as regards consent to the use of cookies.

We publish Google AdSense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the web using the DART cookie. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt out of the AdSense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/ or by using the NAI's (Network Advertising Initiative's) multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. However, these opt-out mechanisms use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.

(6) Cookies and personal information

Cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you, but personal information that we store about you may be linked, by us, to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

(7) Blocking cookies

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. For example:

(a) in Internet Explorer (version 9) you can block cookies using the cookie handling override settings available by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy" and then "Advanced";

(b) in Firefox (version 16) you can block all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Options", "Privacy", selecting "Use custom settings for history" from the drop-down menu, and unticking "Accept cookies from sites"; and

(c) in Chrome (version 23), you can block all cookies by accessing the "Customise and control" menu, and clicking "Settings", "Show advanced settings" and "Content settings", and then selecting "Block sites from setting any data" under the "Cookies" heading.

Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on this website.

(8) Deleting cookies

You can also delete cookies already stored on your computer. For example:

(a) in Internet Explorer (version 9), you must manually delete cookie files (you can find instructions for doing so at http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835

(b) in Firefox (version 16), you can delete cookies by clicking "Tools", "Options", "Privacy" and then "Show Cookies", and then clicking "Remove All Cookies"; and

(c) in Chrome (version 23), you can delete all cookies by accessing the "Customise and control" menu, and clicking "Settings", "Show advanced settings" and "Clear browsing data", and then selecting "Delete cookies and other site and plug-in data" before clicking "Clear browsing data".

Again, doing this may have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.

(9) Cookie preferences

You can manage your preferences relating to the use of cookies on our websites by using your browser cookie ploicy.

(10) Contact us

This website is owned and operated by Qtellwholesale Limited Ireland

If you have any questions about our cookies or this cookies policy, please contact us:

(a) by email (to info@qtellwebdesign.ie)  

The Website Owner, including subsidiaries and affiliates ("Website" or "Website Owner" or "we" or "us" or "our") provides the information contained on this website or any of the pages comprising the website ("website") to visitors ("visitors") (cumulatively referred to as "you" or "your" hereinafter) subject to the terms and conditions set out in these website terms and conditions, the privacy policy and any other relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices which may be applicable to a specific section or module of this website.  
2\. Information on the Website

Whilst every effort is made to update the information contained on this website, neither the Website Owner nor any third party or data or content provider make any representations or warranties, whether express, implied in law or residual, as to the sequence, accuracy, completeness or reliability of information, opinions, any share price information, research information, data and/or content contained on the website (including but not limited to any information which may be provided by any third party or data or content providers) ("information") and shall not be bound in any manner by any information contained on the website. the Website Owner reserves the right at any time to change or discontinue without notice, any aspect or feature of this website. No information shall be construed as advice and information is offered for information purposes only and is not intended for trading purposes. You and your company rely on the information contained on this website at your own risk. If you find an error or omission at this site, please let us know .  
3\. Trade Marks

The trade marks, names, logos and service marks (collectively "trade marks") displayed on this website are registered and unregistered trade marks of the Website Owner. Nothing contained on this website should be construed as granting any licence or right to use any trade mark without the prior written permission of the Website Owner.  
4\. External Links

External links may be provided for your convenience, but they are beyond the control of the Website Owner and no representation is made as to their content. Use or reliance on any external links and the content thereon provided is at your own risk. When visiting external links you must refer to that external websites terms and conditions of use. No hypertext links shall be created from any website controlled by you or otherwise to this website without the express prior written permission of the Website Owner. Please contact us if you would like to link to this website or would like to request a link to your website.  
5\. Public Forums and User Submissions

The Website Owner is not responsible for any material submitted to the public areas by you (which include bulletin boards, hosted pages, chat rooms, or any other public area found on the website. Any material (whether submitted by you or any other user) is not endorsed, reviewed or approved by the Website Owner. The Website Owner reserves the right to remove any material submitted or posted by you in the public areas, without notice to you, if it becomes aware and determines, in its sole and absolute discretion that you are or there is the likelihood that you may, including but not limited to -

5.1 defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the rights of other users or any third parties;

5.2 publish, post, distribute or disseminate any defamatory, obscene, indecent or unlawful material or information;

5.3 post or upload files that contain viruses, corrupted files or any other similar software or programmes that may damage the operation of the Website Owner's and/or a third party's computer system and/or network;

5.4 violate any copyright, trade mark, other applicable Ireland or international laws or intellectual property rights of the Website Owner or any other third party;

5.5 submit contents containing marketing or promotional material which is intended to solicit business.  
6\. Specific Use

You further agree not to use the website to send or post any message or material that is unlawful, harassing, defamatory, abusive, indecent, threatening, harmful, vulgar, obscene, sexually orientated, racially offensive, profane, pornographic or violates any applicable law and you hereby indemnify the Website Owner against any loss, liability, damage or expense of whatever nature which the Website Owner or any third party may suffer which is caused by or attributable to, whether directly or indirectly, your use of the website to send or post any such message or material.  
7\. Warranties

The Website Owner makes no warranties, representations, statements or guarantees (whether express, implied in law or residual) regarding the website, the information contained on the website, your or your company's personal information or material and information transmitted over our system.  
8\. Disclaimer of Liability. 

The Website Owner shall not be responsible for and disclaims all liability for any loss, liability, damage (whether direct, indirect or consequential), personal injury or expense of any nature whatsoever which may be suffered by you or any third party (including your company), as a result of or which may be attributable, directly or indirectly, to your access and use of the website, any information contained on the website, your or your company's personal information or material and information transmitted over our system. In particular, neither the Website Owner nor any third party or data or content provider shall be liable in any way to you or to any other person, firm or corporation whatsoever for any loss, liability, damage (whether direct or consequential), personal injury or expense of any nature whatsoever arising from any delays, inaccuracies, errors in, or omission of any share price information or the transmission thereof, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon or occasioned thereby or by reason of non-performance or interruption, or termination thereof.  
9\. Use of the Website. 

The Website Owner does not make any warranty or representation that information on the website is appropriate for use in any jurisdiction (other than Ireland ). By accessing the website, you warrant and represent to the Website Owner that you are legally entitled to do so and to make use of information made available via the website.  
10\. General  
10.1 Entire Agreement. 

These website terms and conditions constitute the sole record of the agreement between you and the Website Owner in relation to your use of the website. Neither you nor the Website Owner shall be bound by any express tacit or implied representation, warranty, promise or the like not recorded herein. Unless otherwise specifically stated these website terms and conditions supersede and replace all prior commitments, undertakings or representations, whether written or oral, between you and the Website Owner in respect of your use of the website.  
10.2 Alteration

the Website Owner may at any time modify any relevant terms and conditions, policies or notices. You acknowledge that by visiting the website from time to time, you shall become bound to the current version of the relevant terms and conditions (the "current version") and, unless stated in the current version, all previous versions shall be superseded by the current version. You shall be responsible for reviewing the then current version each time you visit the website.  
10.3 Conflict. 

Where any conflict or contradiction appears between the provisions of these website terms and conditions and any other relevant terms and conditions, policies or notices, the other relevant terms and conditions, policies or notices which relate specifically to a particular section or module of the website shall prevail in respect of your use of the relevant section or module of the website.  
10.4 Waiver.

No indulgence or extension of time which either you or the Website Owner may grant to the other will constitute a waiver of or, whether by estoppel or otherwise, limit any of the existing or future rights of the grantor in terms hereof, save in the event or to the extent that the grantor has signed a written document expressly waiving or limiting such rights.  
10.5 Cession. 

The Website Owner shall be entitled to cede, assign and delegate all or any of its rights and obligations in terms of any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices to any third party.  
10.6 Severability.

All provisions of any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices are, notwithstanding the manner in which they have been grouped together or linked grammatically, severable from each other. Any provision of any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices, which is or becomes unenforceable in any jurisdiction, whether due to voidness, invalidity, illegality, unlawfulness or for any reason whatever, shall, in such jurisdiction only and only to the extent that it is so unenforceable, be treated as pro non scripto and the remaining provisions of any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices shall remain in full force and effect.  
10.7 Applicable laws. 

Any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Ireland without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the High Court of Ireland in respect of any disputes arising in connection with the website, or any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices or any matter related to or in connection therewith.  
10.8 Comments or Questions. 

If you have any questions, comments or concerns arising from the website, the privacy policy or any other relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices or the way in which we are handling your personal information please contact us.

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.   
The Information We Collect: 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

Name   
Address   
Phone Number   
The Information We DONT Collect:

Credit/Debit Card Information   
The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.   
Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.   
How You Can Access Or CorrectYour Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by calling us or sending us an email .. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.   
How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us .

Copyright Notice Effective 1 Jan 2006

Copyright Qtellwebdesign Ireland 20011

All aspects of this web site and design, text, graphics, applications, software, underlying source code and all other aspects and are copyright Qtellwebdesign and its affiliates or content and technology providers. 

In accessing these web pages, you agree that any downloading of content is for personal, non-commercial reference only. No part of this web site may be reproduced or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without prior permission of the Website Owner.

For rights clearance please contact us here .  
TradeMarks

TradeMarks are covered in the Terms and Conditions section. Please see also our Privacy Policy.

1\. Introduction

The Website Owner including subsidiaries and affiliates offer website hosting and database hosting services subject to the terms and conditions set out in these terms and conditions, the privacy policy and any other relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices which may be applicable to supply of hosting services.

2\. Glossary of Terms

We includes the Website Owner - Qtellwebdesign - ("Website" or "Website Owner" or "we" or "us" or "our") or any party acting on the Website Owner's implicit instructions.

You ("you", "your", "Customer") includes the person purchasing the services or any party acting on the customer's instructions.

Server means the computer server equipment operated by us in connection with the provision of the Services.

Web Site means the area on the Server allocated by us to you for use by you as a site on the Internet. 

In consideration of the mutual covenants herein, the parties agree to the following, which shall apply during the term of this agreement

3\. Web Site Hosting And Email

3.1 We make no representation and give no warranty as to the accuracy or quality of information received by any person via the Server and we shall have no liability for any loss or damage to any data stored on the Server.  
3.2 You shall effect and maintain adequate insurance cover in respect of any loss or damage to data stored on the Server.  
3.3 You represent, undertake and warrant to us that you will use the Web Site allocated to you only for lawful purposes. In particular, you represent, warrant and undertake to us that.  
3.3.1 You will not use the Server in any manner which infringes any law or regulation or which infringes the rights of any third party, nor will you authorise or permit any other person to do so.  
3.3.2 You will not post, link to or transmit: 

(a) any material which is unlawful, threatening, abusive, malicious, defamatory, obscene, blasphemous, profane or otherwise objectionable in any way.

(b) any material containing a virus or other hostile computer program.

(c) any material which constitutes, or encourages the commission of, a criminal offence or which infringes any patent, trade mark, design right, copyright or any other intellectual property right or similar rights of any person which may subsist under the laws of any jurisdiction.

3.3.3 You will not send bulk email whether opt-in or otherwise from our network. Nor will you promote a site hosted on our network using bulk email.  
3.3.4 You will not employ programs which consume excessive system resources, including but not limited to processor cycles and memory.  
3.4 We reserve the right to remove any material which we deem inappropriate from your web site without notice. We do not host Warez or illegal MP3 content.  
3.5 You shall keep secure any identification, password and other confidential information relating to your account and shall notify us immediately of any known or suspected unauthorised use of your account or breach of security, including loss, theft or unauthorised disclosure of your password or other security information.  
3.6 You shall observe the procedures which we may from time to time prescribe and shall make no use of the Server which is detrimental to our other customers.  
3.7 You shall procure that all mail is sent in accordance with applicable legislation (including data protection legislation) and in a secure manner.  
3.8 In the case of an individual User, you warrant that you are at least 16 years of age and if the User is a company, you warrant that the Services will not be used by anyone under the age of 16 years.  
3.9 Any access to other networks connected to Qtellwebdesign must comply with the rules appropriate for those other networks.  
3.10 While we will use every reasonable endeavour to ensure the integrity and security of the Server, we do not guarantee that the Server will be free from unauthorised users or hackers and we shall be under no liability for non-receipt or misrouting of email or for any other failure of email. 

4\. Service Availability

4.1 We shall use our reasonable endeavours to make available to you at all times the Server and the Services but we shall not, in any event, be liable for interruptions of Service or down-time of the Server.  
4.2 We shall have the right to suspend the Services at any time and for any reason, generally without notice, but if such suspension lasts or is to last for more than 7 days you will be notified of the reason.  
4.3 The Services provided to you hereunder and your account with us cannot be transferred or used by anyone other than you. No more than one log-in session under any one account may be used at any time by you. If you have multiple accounts, you are limited to one login session per system account at any time; user programs may be run only during log-in sessions. If your account is found to have been transferred to another party, or shows other activity in breach of this sub clause, we shall have the right to cancel the account and terminate the Services and/or this Agreement immediately. 

5\. Payment

5.1 All charges payable by you for the Services shall be in accordance with the scale of charges and rates published from time to time by us on our web site and shall be due and payable in advance of our service provision. We reserve the right to change pricing at any time although all pricing is guaranteed for the period of pre payment.  
5.2 Payment is due each anniversary month, quarter or year following the date the Services were established until closure notice is given. If you choose to pay by credit or debit card you authorise Qtellwebdesign to debit your account renewal fees from your card.  
5.3 All payments must be in UK Pounds Sterling, US Dollars or Euros.  
5.4 Without prejudice to our other rights and remedies under this Agreement, if any sum payable is not paid on or before the due date, we shall be entitled forthwith to suspend the provision of Services to you.  
5.5 Once an account has a suspended status, Access to files, databases and other content is explicitly denied. All files, databases and other content including the account itself is permanently deleted after ten days of account suspension.  
5.6 Should access to files, databases and other content be required before they are deleted, account reactivation will be required.

For information on how to order, the payment methods and currencies we accept, and our refund policy, please see Ordering Information .

6\. Termination

6.1 If you fail to pay any sums due to us as they fall due, we may suspend the Services and/or terminate this Agreement forthwith without notice to you.  
6.2 If you break any of these terms and conditions we may suspend the Services and/or terminate this Agreement forthwith without notice to you.  
6.3 If you are a company and you go into insolvent liquidation or suffer the appointment of an administrator or administrative receiver or enter into a voluntary arrangement with your creditors, we shall be entitled to suspend the Services and/or terminate this Agreement forthwith without notice to you.  
6.4 No refunds will be made for Services suspended in accordance with 6.1, 6.2 and 6.3.  
6.5 We reserve the right to suspend the Services and/or terminate this Agreement at any time.  
6.6 You may cancel the Services at any time.  
6.8 Where payment has been made by credit or debit card, any refund will only be issued to the same credit or debit card.  
6.9 On termination of this Agreement or suspension of the Services we shall be entitled immediately to block your Web Site and to remove all data located on it.

7\. Indemnity

7.1 You shall indemnify us and keep us indemnified and hold us harmless from and against any breach by you of these terms of business and any claim brought against us by a third party resulting from the provision of Services by us to you and your use of the Services and the Server including, without limitation, all claims, actions, proceedings, losses, liabilities, damages, costs, expenses (including reasonable legal costs and expenses), howsoever suffered or incurred by us in consequences of your breach or non-observance of this Agreement.

8\. Limitation Of Liability

8.1 All conditions, terms, representations and warranties relating to the Services supplied under this Agreement, whether imposed by statute or operation of law or otherwise, that are not expressly stated in these terms and conditions including, without limitation, the implied warranty of satisfactory quality and fitness for a particular purpose are hereby excluded, subject always to subclause 8.2.  
8.2 Nothing in these terms and conditions shall exclude our liability for death or personal injury resulting from our negligence.  
8.3 Our total aggregate liability to you for any claim in contract, tort, negligence or otherwise arising out of or in connection with the provision of the Services shall be limited to the charges paid by you in respect of the Services which are the subject of any such claim.  
8.4 In any event no claim shall be brought unless you have notified us of the claim within one year of it arising.  
8.5 In no event shall we be liable to you for any loss of business, contracts, profits or anticipated savings or for any other indirect or consequential or economic loss whatsoever 

9\. Revisions

9.1 Qtellwebdesign reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify these Terms and Conditions, and any of our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted in accordance with our Terms and Conditions.

10\. Notices

10.1 Any notice to be given by either party to the other may be sent by either email, fax or recorded delivery to the address of the other party as appearing in this Agreement or ancillary application forms or such other address as such party may from time to time have communicated to the other in writing, and if sent by email shall unless the contrary is proved be deemed to be received on the day it was sent or if sent by fax shall be deemed to be served on receipt of an error free transmission report, or if sent by recorded delivery shall be deemed to be served two days following the date of posting.  
11\. Applicable Law

11.1 This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with Irish law and you hereby submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Irish courts.

12\. Headings

12.1 Headings are included in this Agreement for convenience only and shall not affect the construction or interpretation of this Agreement.

13\. Entire Agreement

13.1 These terms and conditions together with any documents expressly referred to in them, contain the entire Agreement between us relating to the subject matter covered and supersede any previous Agreements, arrangements, undertakings or proposals, written or oral: between us in relation to such matters. No oral explanation or oral information given by any party shall alter the interpretation of these terms and conditions. In agreeing to these terms and conditions, you have not relied on any representation other than those expressly stated in these terms and conditions and you agree that you shall have no remedy in respect of any misrepresentation which has not been made expressly in this Agreement.

14\. Comments or Questions. 

14.1 If you have any questions, comments or concerns arising from the website, the privacy policy or any other relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices or the way in which we are handling your personal information please contact us .

http://www.website-law.co.uk/ourdocumentlicence.html

Privacy Policy 

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. 

(1) What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

[(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including [your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views]);]

[(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including [DETAILS]);]

[(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including [DETAILS]);]

[(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including [DETAILS]);]

[(e) any other information that you choose to send to us; and]

[(f) OTHER INFORMATION.] 

[(2) Cookies 

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We [may] use [both] [“session” cookies] [and “persistent” cookies] on the website. [We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and [OTHER USES].] [We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; [OTHER USES].] 

[Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.] [Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.]

[We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.] 

[Our [advertisers/payment services providers] may also send you cookies.] 

[We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.] 

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites[, including this one].]

(3) Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

[(a) administer the website;]

[(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;]

[(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;]

[(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;]

[(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;]

[(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;]

[(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;]

[(h) send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications relating to our business [or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications) ;]

[(i) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;]

[(j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and]

[(k) OTHER USES.] 

(4) Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

[(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.]

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

[(5) International data transfers 

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries [(including [the United States], [Japan], [OTHER COUNTRIES])] which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Areas (EEA). 

[In addition, [personal information that you submit for publication on the website] will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.]

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.]

(6) Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

[We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted [using SSL technology].] 

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

[You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.] 

(7) Policy amendments 

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

[We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.] 

(8) Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £20.00).

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

(9) Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

(10) Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

(11) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to [info@qtellwebdesign.ie] or by post to [9 Glen Abhainn Lawns Enfield Co Meath Ireland]. 

(12) Data controller

The data controller responsible for our website is [Qtellwholesale Limited]. 

Our data protection registration number is [CRO Number 463653]. 

This privacy policy is courtesy of  
Employment Law Contracts and Website Law
